http://www.webster.ac.at/data-privacy/index.html

Webster Vienna Privacy, Cookie and GDPR Information | Webster Vienna Private University
Webster Vienna Privacy, Cookie and GDPR Information
Privacy Statement »
Cookie Policy »
GDPR Compliance and Privacy Notices
Your privacy is important to us and we take the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other relevant privacy regulations seriously. It is our goal to be sensitive
and respectful of your personal information and to adhere to all facets of the GDPR
regulation. Please be aware that all personal data you provide are subject to our
Privacy Notices.
We have created Privacy Notices for our main constituents that reflect our commitment
to transparency and best practice when it comes to handling your personal data. In
the Notices, we outline how we collect your data, why we collect your data, when we
share your data, and inform you of your rights with regard to access, deletion and
the ability to update that data.
We strongly encourage you to read our Privacy Notices in its entirety to understand
Webster’s privacy practices in advance of submitting any personal information to us.
If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Notices or any of our related privacy
policies, please do not hesitate to contact the campus Privacy Manager or Webster’s
Office of Privacy and Information Security by phone or email using the contact details provided at the end of this page.
Privacy Notices
Student Privacy Notice
Alumni and Friends Privacy Notice
Employee, Adjunct Faculty, and Employee Applicant Privacy Notice
Webster Vienna Facebook Privacy Notice
More Information
If you have questions about our Privacy Notices, our cookie policy, privacy practices,
or any other aspect of your privacy and the security of your personal information,
please contact our Privacy Manager by phone (+43 269 9293 0) or email gdpr[at]webster.ac.at.
You may also write to us at:
Webster UniversityOffice of Privacy and Information SecurityInformation Security
Employee, Adjunct Faculty, and Employee Applicant Privacy Notice
Employee, Adjunct Faculty, and Employee Applicant Privacy Notice
Facebook Privacy Notice
SHARE THIS PAGE:
Webster Vienna Private University Palais Wenkheim Praterstr. 23, 1020 Vienna, Austria info@webster.ac.at | +43 (0)1 - 269 92 93 - 0
© 2020 Webster University
2020 Opening Hours: Monday – Thursday 8:00am -10:00pm | Friday 8:00am-7:30pm
Information For:
Information for:
Task navigation
©
